

SHAILY GANDHI

UX/UI designer

CONTACT

shailymgandhi@gmail.com

shaily.design

in linkedin.com/in/shaily-gandhi

+31 6 84480755

SKILLS

UX design
UI design
Prototyping and Wireframing
Problem solving
User research
User interviews & testing

TOOLS

Figma / Sketch / Miro / Adobe XD / Photoshop / AutoCAD / ARCHICAD / Revit / Google Sketchup / Invision

EDUCATION

UX/UI Bootcamp Ironhack, Amsterdam 2021 - Current

Bachelors of Architecture CEPT University, Ahmedabad 2007 - 2013

Student Exchange Program TUM, Munich. 2011

PROFILE

I find the underlying concepts of Architecture & UX design very similar - from research to documentation to team dynamics and construction.

My approach to design is very grounded in user research and focused on human experience rather than just building a product and environment.

I am a designer, dedicated to work towards achieving goals and to carefully create products that bring positive change into people's lives.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Designer

April 2018 - October 2020

KENK Architecten B.V., Amsterdam

- Worked on various large scale projects, including luxury apartments with commercial spaces, student housing, multi-family housing, housing for the refugees.
- Worked on all the design process which includes working from preliminary design phase, building permit drawings to the construction drawings.
- A great experience learning about the Users from Dutch housing market.

Associate Architect

Keystone Architects, Bangalore

November 2015 - September 2017

- Led several small scale residential, commercial & hospitality projects
- As part of the design team, met clients & discussed the creative & analytical design process
- Prepared detailed drawings & managed site execution for several projects
- Analysed cost & benefits of the projects

Junior Architect

footprints E.A.R.T.H., Ahmedabad

October 2013 - September 2014

- · Worked on various design, competition projects
- Model-making

